(Howard:)We were 15... I just said,
"Don't say it."
(Emily:)No, it's okay.
(Emily:)He told me that story
a long time ago.
Raj!
(Raj:)It was our first date,
(Raj:)there was an
awkward silence.
(Howard:)What was I
supposed to say?
(gasps)
(Penny:)Oh, it's beautiful.
(Leonard:)Oh, the girls really
did a nice job.
(Howard:)Aw...
(Penny:)I know I wasn't
into this before,
(Penny:)but I'm so glad I get
to take you to your first prom.
(Leonard:)What makes you think
I didn't go to my prom?
(Sheldon:)I went.
Well, who'd you go with?
(Leonard:)I took a little lady
I like to call loneliness.
(Howard:)Aw...
Aw, it's all right.
(Leonard:)We ended up having a threesome
(Leonard:)with her friend humiliation,
so...
(Penny:)Well, if I would have been
there and saw you alone,
(Penny:)I would've asked you
to dance.
(Leonard:)No, you wouldn't have.
(Penny:)Well, you don't
know that.
(Leonard:)It was before
my growth spurt.
(Penny:)What, that already happened?
(imitates laughter)
(Leonard:)Very funny.
(Penny:)Well, you wouldn't
have asked me either.
(Leonard:)I would have asked you.
(scoffs)